MaRisa Jackson

Nashville, TN | (812) 493-5555 | mhljackson@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Product Manager with 4 years of SaaS startup experience. Worked as a software developer before transitioning to a product manager. Applied my development background and user-centered methods to create great products that grew annual recurring revenues from **\$0** to **\$4MM** and active users from **0** to **50,000**+.

EXPERIENCE

GameWisp, Remote

Product Manager

APRIL 2017 - PRESENT

- Designed, developed, and managed products that grew annual recurring revenue from **\$0 to \$4MM**.
- Conceptualized, directed, and launched three different B2B & B2B2C SaaS products.
- Designed and developed data collection tools to extract and interpret user data from **50,000+ active users**.
- Managed five full time employees and several contact hires across engineering, design, and data collection.
- Leveraged user feedback to iterate on existing features, doubling on platform daily active users.

Software Developer / Lead Software Developer DECEMBER 2014 - APRIL 2017

- Served as engineering point of contact for the executive team, reporting directly to the CTO.
- Oversaw all engineering development across GameWisp's suite of products.
- Instituted best practices for our engineering team, including Git Flow, QA, and Agile methodologies.

PROJECTS

Recurring Billing System (WebApp, GameWisp) - Industry-leading payment processing software that flawlessly processed hundreds of thousands of dollars of transactions per month

Reward Management System (WebApp, GameWisp) - Fulfillment system used by businesses and consumers to send, receive, and track rewards. Utilizes multiple APIs including Twitch and Discord.

Admin Management System (WebApp, GameWisp) - Internal administrative portal for non-technical teams (support, accounting, marketing) to perform their duties at scale

ConcertWire (WebApp, Independent) - Music app that utilizes the Ticketmaster and Spotify APIs to create a playlist based on upcoming concerts

LANGUAGES AND TOOLS

- SQL, Laravel, PHP, Ruby on Rails, Javascript, CSS, HTML, SASS, KnockoutJS, Node.js, Vue.js
- MixPanel, FullStory, Intercom, Google Analytics, Basecamp, Trello, Github, JIRA

EDUCATION

Nashville Software School, Nashville, TN

APRIL 2014 - SEPTEMBER 2014

Six month full-time intensive software development program: full stack Node.js and Rails projects